<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book version="5.0" xml:id="spring-security-reference-guide" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
    xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" 
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook http://www.docbook.org/xml/5.0/xsd/docbook.xsd
    http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink http://www.docbook.org/xml/5.0/xsd/xlink.xsd">
    <bookinfo>
        <title>Parancoe Meta-Framework</title>
        <subtitle>Reference Guide</subtitle>
        <authorgroup>
            <author>
                <firstname>Lucio</firstname>
                <surname>Benfante</surname>
            </author>
        </authorgroup>
        <releaseinfo>2.x</releaseinfo>
        <legalnotice>
            <para>Copies of this document may be made for your own use and for
            distribution to others, provided that you do not charge any
            fee for such copies and further provided that each copy
            contains this Copyright Notice, whether distributed in print
            or electronically.</para>
        </legalnotice>
    </bookinfo>
    <toc/>
    <preface xml:id="introduction">
        <title>Introduction</title>
        <para>Parancoe is a project aiming to simplify the release of web
        applications promoting the convention over configuration philosophy
        and the DRY principle. This project is promoted by the JUG Padova,
        and everybody can partecipate.
        </para>
        <para>Parancoe is a Java meta-framework aggregating in an useful way
        Hibernate/JPA, Spring 2, Spring MVC and, for the AJAX support, DWR.
        </para>
        <para>Parancoe purpose is to give to developers a set of libraries
        ready to build standard web applications (which in most cases are just
        crud applications) without worrying of long and harmful configurations
        files. Parancoe will be composed of a full MVC stack.
        </para>
        <para>Parancoe is open source and is released under the Apache License,
        Version 2.0.
        </para>
        <para>Are you interested in the parancoe word meaning? A “parancoa” is
        a scaffolding in the dialect of the Venice (Italy) area.
        </para>
    </preface>
    <part xml:id="getting-started">
        <title>Getting Started</title>
        <partintro>
            <para>This part of this guid will introduce at using Parancoe,
            in particular how to start a now web project, how to add a simple
            controller and how to add a simple form to your application.
            </para>
        </partintro>
        <xi:include href="startANewProject.xml" />
    </part>
</book>